[
    {
        "question": "What are the check-in requirements?",
        "answer": "{CheckInRequirement}"
    },
    {
        "question": "At what time can I check in?",
        "answer": "{CheckInTime}"
    },
    {
        "question": "At what hour do I check out?",
        "answer": "{CheckOutTime}"
    },
    {
        "question": "Arrive early than {CheckInTime},  is it possible?",
        "answer": "{EarlyCheckIn}"
    },
    {
        "question": "Can I check-in ahead of {CheckInTime}?",
        "answer": "{EarlyCheckIn}"
    },
    {
        "question": "Can I check-in before {CheckInTime}?",
        "answer": "{EarlyCheckIn}"
    },
    {
        "question": "Can I check-out after {CheckOutTime}?",
        "answer": "{LateCheckOut}"
    },
    {
        "question": "Can I leave past {CheckOutTime}?",
        "answer": "{LateCheckOut}"
    },
    {
        "question": "Is it possible to check-out after {CheckOutTime}?",
        "answer": "{LateCheckOut}"
    },
    {
        "question": "How much do your rooms cost?",
        "answer": "{RoomPrices}"
    },
    {
        "question": "How much do your single rooms cost?",
        "answer": "{RoomPricesSingle}"
    },
    {
        "question": "How much do your double rooms cost?",
        "answer": "{RoomPricesDouble}"
    },
    {
        "question": "How much do your connecting rooms cost?",
        "answer": "{RoomPricesConnecting}"
    },
    {
        "question": "What types of rooms do you have?",
        "answer": "{RoomTypes}"
    },
    {
        "question": "How can I book a room?",
        "answer": "{RoomBooking}"
    }
]
